schedule an appointment with your doctor
and there's a Clark doing that as part
of the scheduling you also a car is
going to be sick that's kind of like a
high level application that we'll be
able to use they the underlying
transportation plan but that's also from
a hacker perspective and I can add you
to that and trigger a bad team commander
so basically the duh the end result of
our solutions is we call that incidence
of the cybersecurity incidence probably
would be a little hard to read but you
can see this is one example our product
is used by something another trend ugly
scene Ottawa which is
the building of a security operation
center which is where the surface of
being monitor is being tracked after
violation in this specific instance we
see a stop engine command that was sent
to the fleet at a bad time at that time
could be like as the people is driving
you're not supposed to about an etic
kill engine for me that's actually a
feature in some of the telematics
providers have but it's only enabled in
places like South America but in the
u.s. it's not illegal to use that to use
that specific feature so they disable it
in to cover but what the hacker gets in
and even if they weren't supposed to do
that something
that we're looking to find together the
key idea is to find it you know not
after it already took place but like
after the horses that were born that
meant some ladies trying to play with a
lot and we give like it's like an early
detection facility where the Oleum tent
work for those lead operators so Mike my
last slide pretty much this having said
all that security and I think anybody
that's that's been into space there's no
you know one solution that is assault
everything it's like there's there's a
concept called defense in depth and this
in this area we look at lead vehicle
security is something that will find
this way makes me to be equals over time
definitely not today there's I don't
think there's
Tesla they haven't publicized whether
they have it they have liked it some
elements of a people components but I
don't think there's there's many others
that have implemented that inside their
cars it will be a part of the overall
solution over time but we see the place
that most aliens are starting is
disliked about base where you can
actually have a level of detection which
is what it's actually prescribed work
for the automakers you can happen today
if you have a basement data that you're
already collecting and this is the only
way to actually offer protection across
the fleet and not only individual
vehicles would we see both of these
solutions working together and
ultimately be consumed by when you see
here in the sock which i think is you
know the acceleration of the stocks
being built product but it was we dived
across the world
I think us may be ahead of the curve by
affecting
like a huge other thing for them yes
again preciate all of your information
is there's a lot to go through here we
don't have a lot of time but let's just
talk real quick so couple things your
company finds things happening in dis
numbers misbehavior
solution for everyone out there how what
is the role of it I mean is it a
subscriber only it's everyone
so we sell to two types of constituents
one is OEMs we some of them directly and
we sell to OEM a OMB does not benefit
and if they're not our custom because
it's away of the data and we will
predict their vehicles based and the
other constituent that we have is
complete it's not only isolates like
enterprises that have connected people
police trucks or our companies that's
very similar but a slightly different
organization but it's basically they
they share the same problem because if
you know I was during lunch I was
telling this example imagine something
like the FedEx late day before Christmas
somebody accidentally nope no driver can
turn on the FedEx what I was thinking
this all the presses were coming to me
there but what are they herded - OH -
whoa
yeah but what about you know again this
whole conversation we've been having
about you know how important it is and
again I understand collaborates from the
CRC and everyone said this is but a
certain extent as we're talking about
our learnings on the autonomous cars on
parts of that works and don't work or
processes or algorithms on the other end
on the cybersecurity you know that all
of a sudden you realize oh my gosh this
product or or double or om you're going
after or they're going after the breaks
north of the steering you know that type
of thing is that become a shared economy
to work where does that what's the
balance between you being an independent
company and you know that's you helping
out so we share with the community in
the community shares with us and there's
been you know I think just last week we
were at Auto eyes that which is a data
sharing environment or both
for vendors to share share finding
spirit we're part of that having said
that I think with anybody even you know
we can find things it's not to say that
you look let's say we're serving okay if
he does not have capabilities to do
something with things that we found we
can share it and they might know about
know and they might not be able to do
anything about it and if you have I mean
we're not number of poems or tabs or in
the danger zone
we've published privately nada nada the
public I can tell you that you know be
from this base the I wouldn't say like
the best like the nation's some some of
the components not the best title
security practices have used and was
rated so things that we know in the IT
side do not so true
and here's you still see it like so it's
so happy we know it didn't happen for
well people I'm talking about how the
the components were created so things
like no encryption on the data transfer
using UDP binary like kind of like basic
stuff are still there because you
haven't you have trucks that have you
know somebody put a dongle into five
years ago I thought about cider
latest and we got around after you still
seeing people be lazy or not being this
exciting I think there's way more on
understanding today things are
definitely improving but you still have
coding cars and that is very old but
final question on the test that you
brought them up and of course one of the
things with someone unique and then a
single box architecture
it says the way the future is that
prettily
a confident way to avoid this type of
thing I think Tesla are I said GM is
ahead of the curve I think Tesla are the
most ahead of the curve they have they
are red team which is kind of like the
way that they tried to attack himself
bigger than anybody else's in the space
they the poverty since it's like 2011
nobody you would've read to us probably
some of the aliens back then so they are
that's one of their approaches they're
using you know another thing that was
announces like how they use bounties
which is like you pay actors or quite
has to try to attack you and find
vulnerabilities which is some very
common practice in the enterprise side
they are one of the leaders produc know
and I think that those types of things
are what helps them become more mature
in terms of security but I think their
code is there a software company at
heart yeah
damn of course we're out of time I
really pleased and to introduce our next
speaker please welcome Anton to the
stage in time it's an important river
with wise he does something out there in
the media world what we won't tell me
what it is but I know I'm gonna stone in
front of sliders already next feature of
course me to introduction to rich folks
he was here two years ago as our
involvement I think he showed one of the
earlier versions of this product which
much much better level to driving
experience you obviously want to hear
where the project that's gone and for
instance now and what the strategies
going forward another thing that
happened in October of 2016 was
something closely related
my entry
system at a press conference right here
in town and sort of read you the very
first sentence that Elin law said at the
press conference and that be the
background to what we might expect from
upgrades in the future any senator basic
news here is that all cars exiting the
factory have hardware necessary for
levels by autonomy so that's in terms of
cameras compute power it's an entry car
we made on the order two thousand where
so we can are shipping at home with
level five literally meaning hardware
capable of full self-driving for
driverless capability so we've almost
would love to hear if a product
aftermarket product that someone maybe
just George's Lord somebody else could
develop would possibly deliver on a
level five litter the promise that he
lost beta two years ago
[Applause]
[Music]
research but yeah
Shifa wanna stop actually should stop we
should pick stuff in the space big balls
that open-source RHD maps that make
mapping companies cry a little release
HD maps are everywhere in the United
States but the NBN and they drop a
little for the year so these are
entirely active users so we have we have
the second largest connected meet so
we're getting that video take a cam data
and we're actually you know
[Music]
if your car does make a mistake you can
but this is what it looks like when
you're inside the car you can see even
in this residential Road if you take
that curve quite nicely we also have
tried Margaret I have to be refreshed by
the way Google Translate lookup
self-driving cars in fact the top peak
self-driving cars was the organic so you
don't think about that you're like
really dark and potentially we don't
make sure they pay attention we ship
drug monitoring not just a new product
but retroactive leave our products then
we trade small models that we can
actually share with our devices can a
normal scale to level 4 but
unfortunately not really that's why
research to solve this problem the green
is the map the blue and the yellow are
the lanes and then we just have cars
weapons but this little problem with
this approach our latent cars are fakes
there's no such actual there's no
physics based definition of a lane of
the car the only temperatures we have
planes and cars are like human based
definitions and the problem with those
are hard to ground
CCO the bathroom on this slide is
automatically generated none of this
ground truth is done by and labeling us
like a seventy five point seven billion
miles of data we get a note back we
automatically grab it and we training
behavioral models up drive well ideally
we drink mechanical model of driving
that's your really good
or we cheat a little bit down to avoid
your opponent by using weights on the
legs apart eventually motivation that's
what we're working on income research
three open source HD max you see here
this is just about San Francisco where
we have sufficient coverage to generate
the mass and this is what it looks like
you can see these restrooms this green
clover this green prostitutes here and
each one of those is a picture that we
got back from our video world local logs
and all these pictures so that happened
in accuracy and with tons of pictures
localized to half a meter accuracy you
can post process that character HD maps
but at ten centimeters of accuracy you
say okay how's this different of HD not
a company that's out there every
generation you have a company that's out
there has to pay money to get parts
they're completely lost stem money
record for that tribute car we had the
argument we can pay people pay to the
world we're gonna get the mouse away for
free we have to rent the post processing
software anyway to do they are mattad
random true thing so yeah here are
complicated the advanced commands come
enter into a business development
this is last year's model sell sell
track markets we sell software many
believer in people
when you're in the business is so
expensive to be the premium meal that's
just how much we're cutting prices here
it coming on when people are like eighty
on gold that's so futuristic that can't
be available anytime soon no no it's
available right away in fact we will
have a mobile shop set up outside we
must become $4.99 and my gaming goals
they'll bake yourself right now you can
put them in a Honda and open source
software yeah
for supercruise nothing looks like once
in your car and maybe they're talking
for the question
[Music]
GNN research alex net all into object
classification before that right this is
like you're trying to move flour from
here here and all the spheres aren't if
you make the right decisions you budget
your speed to do it right sometimes
yellow is boiled in this if you were so
in San Francisco
in this area meaning the tire
engineering standpoint is when you're on
a slippery surface in your cornering and
you know things are starting to happen
the vehicle that you know again most of
us but should be react in a certain way
how does something like this know we
don't do anything with that and we will
disengage in fact if your car activates
traction control system we don't
I'll stop in the car all that stuff is
still manufacturer and who detect that
TCS engaged we get a microphone with
Jorge what happens this will stick to
this dashcam in a dump car or on this
mouth supported can useful engine
so we also have over there the mobile
star we have great pianist great and
there's our client decision GPS but none
of the mapping stuff relies on the other
stuff in the car that's all done with
just stuff built into the ER and stock
builder to be right and also far forward
collision warning that our driver
monitor don't depend on the car so you
still get those features in every part
other questions out there later parts
from understood right here the one
[Music]
so right now we're using the camera and
the radar I think that graters interplay
of diminishing role over time I think
you can do it almost all cameras because
that's a and people are the only example
of our tracking system existence so I
think they don't really need radar again
in the less sensors you can use clusters
to fail I think maps are a great check
maps you can do you can do functional
safety and that's the ways you can turn
functional safety and say education
system so mask you know you can say that
if you're on the stretch of highway
never allowed to be able to do this so
it can you time here for your product in
just our car the most recent speakers
are two before that that have to do with
like again cybersecurity Cisco I think
most of the cybersecurity industry and
systemic I used to work in this industry
right oh you have my book we have safety
and security the same thing they're not
and let me tell you why
safety is protecting from a random
attack security is protecting from a
targeted attack security is in
[Music]
after-market
entry into a vehicle system would seem
like if there was a possibility that I
couldn't open a door - right like what
would the trick poverty in this case
once again if I somehow got through to
your product and I could have your cars
just stopped up a road or get away or
not
so these Safety's not them on this
device is all of our Mis devices that
this device will detect if you press
home and guess that'll work right now
and it will prevent that twice we
sending any signals to the car but the
safety is not here pretty compromised
this device
here it's probably not again if you
can't build secure code you just have to
raise the attacker bar at a point that
it's not worth it for them the automatic
system at that point but um regardless
like there just aren't these evil
malicious people out there this is why
the whole cybersecurity industry is kind
of
[Applause]
[Laughter]
we're doing a periscope right now we're
gonna show up
showed everything so this is a neon gold
people you can see their beautiful
devices yeah we got a cooling fan
solution look at this grill alright
look at the improvement look at the
improvement here you remember how it
used to have those terrible screws on
the top it looked a little janky look
this ankle fits in check out this
beautiful gold the thermal is a bit
better on this than the EON - I think if
you buy any own gold you'll be quite
happy
there's the accessory bag that comes
with it we got two lengths a USB cable
we got a sim tool we got to go for a
mount with the VHP yeah Charlie's good
charging is great well that's why we
don't ship the extension cable we
shipped six book so therefore 99 no
one's bought anything yeah I think it
kind of reminds us of the self-driving
car but plenty of already ordered if you
haven't bought one of these will ship
this out to you like Thursday maybe
we'll even ship it out tomorrow
we couldn't ship it out tomorrow we
can't rip it up tomorrow thing I'm not
gonna make any promises
yeah we need from a civil ship before
Thursday yeah that's the promise I will
make yeah they're great they're really
nice and you know we were really looking
for growth yeah that's why they we
dropped this price so crazy low
yes we love girl fell over engineering
it's easier now than ever um so we have
a great we have a great community on
slack who've created tutorials and
YouTube videos and if you can like you
take a Saturday you won't have it you'll
have it ready to go honestly if you know
what you're doing it's a five minute
install but to really like read
everything you'll need to get the speed
it's not even 4:00 it's a weekend
morning you'll be out cruising you can
see through good stuff you can't just
sell anything it's all right when you do
the hard work we we make hardware for
less money than we sell it for and then
we make a profit I know this is a crazy
business model in Silicon Valley today
yeah but this is what we do these a lot
of these companies here I don't really
understand like they hired this thing
called business development
yes we don't do that we just like we
make product and then we posted on the
website at more price than it cost us to
make product and then we bake and we
want to sell more products so yeah yeah
yeah it's not fans of that was it's a
two-year company of a small company with
like 10 ish people and that's exactly
what comment is now and it was just I
never disagreed with what Ilan said I
knew that like you know obviously what I
had in the garage wasn't ready to go to
market and this honestly it's still a
developer is it is it a consumer product
will be there will be there he's a plan
the plan is obvious but everything takes
time and he wants us to hear so
realistically the timeline is that for
four years so Ilan is right it's nice to
know that Ilan is not just wrong about
his timelines he's wrong about other
people's time I do but hey he's an
optimist works it works and it motivates
you right like did I think it was two
hours
again those really really showing off
and get in your orders right now before
we sell out there's only a limited
number is only a limited number of
beyond golds in the world calling
limited number of lay eCos in the world
so we bought the ball we literally
bought them all and show them look it
comes with a little bag and a big bag
get on right now oh the bucket shop it's
at oh man no no no we're really like
this is a box yeah this is a nice good
beer yeah you get one of these you're
like I feel good yeah
George are we being open about the phone
that it runs through yeah Lee you can
buy one of those and try to use it
yeah actually gold yeah the phone is
gold
yeah or take a look and if you can't see
the gold you can call it it is 64
correct short size 64 yes hopefully
someone got all this information right
on the website I think so this product
doesn't come without the market this
product comes at the dashcam if you want
to install all the pilot you have to do
that yourself
yeah for legal from a legal perspective
we don't sell any hardware that old your
car we just sell general
Elster
of course intact in fact it goes even
beyond that we have driver model so this
camera will actually watch you while you
drive to make sure yes and if you're
engaged and your eyes are off the road
bbbbbb y de new ver have that in fact we
didn't have it before
uber either with the uber and Tesla
crashes that happened this year that
we're like okay we gotta get serious and
within six weeks we turned around driver
Bob berry and it's it's hitting a par
with jams it's industry
Jean used supergroups not only when they
assistant engage I'm super cruise GM's
good level to chickpeas linked on the
website are only our galaxy to see it
$5.00 Adam oh yeah so we have Kronberg
we have gorgeous cards we know you can
you can body you can buy a t-shirt for
$20
[Music]